(Wil:)I'm really happy to do this for you...
(Wil:)...but not if she's gonna be a huge
pain in the ass the whole time.
Are you gonna let him speak to me
like that?
(Wil:)Well...
(Sheldon:)...you're my girlfriend,
and I don't want you to be upset.
(Sheldon:)Then again, Wil Wheaton's my friend,
and I don't want him to be upset.
(Sheldon:)Hmm...
(Sheldon:)This is a sticky wicket.
(Sheldon:)What do you think?
(Amy:)Can I speak to you for a second?
(Sheldon:)I'll be right back.
(Sheldon:)Feel free to play with yourself.
(Amy:)I don't care for your friend,
and he's being rude to me.
(Amy:)You need to ask him to leave.
(Sheldon:)Amy, I can't just ask Wil Wheaton to leave.
(Sheldon:)He's a minor celebrity.
(Sheldon:)Once you explain who he is,
many people recognize him.
(Amy:)Fine, then maybe I should go.
(Sheldon:)Could you? That would solve everything.
(Sheldon:)You are the best.
I'll see you at dinner tonight?
(Amy:)Sure you wouldn't rather have dinner
with your friend Wil Wheaton?
(Sheldon:)Come to think of it, I would.
(Sheldon:)You, little lady, are on fire.